<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MacOS on Home</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/macos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MacOS on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/macos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MacBook A1181 with only 2GB and TrueNAS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/macbook-truenas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/macbook-truenas/</guid>
      <description>Decided to have a Time Machine server at home, but the simplest solution didn&amp;rsquo;t work so I took an old MacBook (A1181) out of retirement to use it as a TrueNAS server.&#xA;Introduction I tried to create a new server to only run a small instance of TrueNAS locally but it didn&amp;rsquo;t work. The computer is just too old for the job, with only 2GB of RAM it can&amp;rsquo;t sustain the service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time to say goodbye to my 10 year old MacBook Pro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/good-bye-macbook-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/good-bye-macbook-pro/</guid>
      <description>After 10 years of use, it is time to let go of this reliable machine and embrace a somewhat unknown future of the Apple Silicon. Last Sunday I bought a brand new MacBook Air M2 because it was really cheap, being offered for less than half of the price on Apple Store. Over the years I had many reasons to postpone this purchase and part of these reasons have been the fact that this MacBook has beee so reliable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 years using the MacBook Pro 9,2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/macbook-pro-10years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/macbook-pro-10years/</guid>
      <description>The MacBook Pro 9,2 is a model of the MacBook Pro that was released in June 2012. It has a 13.3-inch display, a 2.5 GHz or 2.9 GHz dual-core Intel Core i5 or i7 processor, 4 GB or 8 GB of RAM, and a 500 GB or 750 GB hard drive.&#xA;My MacBook was bought around 2013 or 2014, don&amp;rsquo;t remember exactly. It was bought new, with 4GB of RAM and 500 GB hard drive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
