<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorial on Home</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/tutorial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorial on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 11:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Obsidian &#43; Copilot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/10_obsidian-copilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/10_obsidian-copilot/</guid>
      <description>I needed an easy and cheap option to integrate my vault with artificial intelligence. The easiest option could be to pay for subscriptions, which would be a high cost for me, since I am would not use the service that often to justify. Another option would be to pay for a Cloud GPU service to run big queries that would be unfeasible to run locally. This option seemed too cumbersome for my case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPIpy v1 - Release</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rpipy_v1_release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 23:52:23 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rpipy_v1_release/</guid>
      <description>Brief summary paragraph&#xA;Introduction Arguments Conclusion You can reach out to contact me about this and other topics at my email lucas.fernandes.df@gmail.com or by filling the form below.&#xA;Your email: Your message: Send </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Oracle Cloud Free tier</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/oracle_cloud_free_tier/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 22:33:19 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/oracle_cloud_free_tier/</guid>
      <description>The problem This week I have been searching for solutions to use domains with my applications running in containers in my MacBook Pro server. Yes, I have converted my MacBook Pro into a server, at least for now. The first solution was to use a Pi-Hole as a local DNS and it works fine, but the problem is that I have to specify ports to get into the applications and it gets annonying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;{{ replace .File.ContentBaseName `-` ` ` | title }}&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/draft/obsidian-&#43;-copilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/draft/obsidian-&#43;-copilot/</guid>
      <description>I needed a easy and cheap way to integrate my vault with artificial intelligence. One of the ways would be to pay for subscriptions, which would be a high cost for me, since I am would not use the service that often. Another way would be to pay for a Cloud GPU service to run big queries, that would be unfeasible to run locally. Eventually I discovered OpenRouter, which seems to be the easiest to solution because I can access multiple models at a single place and also have a API that I can connect to other services.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
